Jester Hairston Collection MS040
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Sound recordings related to Jester Hairston, 1940 -- 1990; 1960 -- 1980; MS040.001; 20.4 Linear Feet; 9 Digital Object(s)
  - First annual Archdiocesan high school choral & instrumental festival, 1961; MS040.001.005.00002; Los Angeles Archdiocesan High School Chorus (Box 5)
    Hairston featured as conductor./ Saugus, CA./ Century Record ./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - First annual Archdiocesan high school choral & instrumental festival, 1961; MS040.001.005.00003; Los Angeles Archdiocesan High School Chorus (Box 5)
    Hairston featured as conductor./ Signed by Bill Barclay./ Saugus, CA./ Century Record ./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - First annual Archdiocesan high school choral & instrumental festival, 1961; MS040.001.005.00004; Los Angeles Archdiocesan High School Chorus (Box 5)
  - First annual Archdiocesan high school choral & instrumental festival, 1961; MS040.001.005.00005; Los Angeles Archdiocesan High School Chorus (Box 5)
  - First annual Archdiocesan high school choral & instrumental festival, 1961; MS040.001.005.00006; Los Angeles Archdiocesan High School Chorus (Box 5)
  - First annual Archdiocesan high school choral & instrumental festival, 1961; MS040.001.005.00007; Los Angeles Archdiocesan High School Chorus (Box 5)
  - First annual Archdiocesan high school choral & instrumental festival, 1961; MS040.001.005.00008; Los Angeles Archdiocesan High School Chorus (Box 5)
  - The first family, 1962; MS040.001.005.00009; Meader, Vaughn (Box 5)
    Inscribed to Hairston by unknown persons./ New York./ Cadence./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Foothill College, 1964; MS040.001.005.00010; The Skyline Chorale (Box 5)
    Hairston featured as artist, soloist, conductor, and commentator./ Inscribed to Hairston by the Skyline Chorale and Foothill Singers./ [United States]./ Custom Recording by Westmont./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - For thee I sing, 1965; MS040.001.005.00011; Harbor Masters (Box 5)
    Signed by Jim Buell./ This date is approximate./ Santa Cruz, CA./ Radiant Song Records./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Galloping on my dinosaur and other fun songs for children, 1964; MS040.001.005.00012; Thor, Larry (Box 5)
    Inscribed to Marge and Jester Hairston by Larry Thor./ This date is approximate./ [New York]./ Harmony./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Give me Jesus, 1977; MS040.001.006.00001; Holman United Methodist Church (Box 6)
    Hairston featured as artist./ This date is approximate./ Pasadena, CA./ Audio Engineering Associates./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - God's church is alive, 1976; MS040.001.006.00002; Landrum, B.J. (Box 6)
    Signed by Rev. B.J. Landrum./ [United States]./ [S.I.]./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - The Grand Island City Singers and the Northwest High School A Capella Choir presents "Jester and the Singers", 1972; MS040.001.006.00003; Grand Island City Singers (Box 6)
    Hairston featured as artist and soloist./ [Nebraska]./ [Sound Factory]./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Grand festival concert, 1971; MS040.001.006.00004; [Utah] All-state Chorus (Box 6)
    Hairston featured as artist and guest conductor./ Specific concert date is: 8 October 1971./ [Utah]./ [S.I.]./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Grand festival concert, 1971; MS040.001.006.00005; [Utah] All-state Chorus (Box 6)
  - Grand festival concert, 1971; MS040.001.006.00006; [Utah] All-state Chorus (Box 6)
  - Grand festival concert, 1971; MS040.001.006.00007; [Utah] All-state Chorus (Box 6)
  - Grand festival concert, 1971; MS040.001.006.00008; [Utah] All-state Orchestra; [Utah] All-state Band (Box 6)
  - Grand festival concert, 1971; MS040.001.006.00009; Unknown (Box 6)
  - Granite School District, 1975; MS040.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
    Hairston featured as artist and guest conductor./ Salt Lake City, UT./ DRC./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Great Day!, 1981; MS040.001.006.00011; Victor Valley Community College Chorus and College Singers (Box 6)
    Hairston featured as artist and guest conductor./ Huntington Station, NY./ Silver Crest Custom./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Great Instrumental Christmas Music, 1978; MS040.001.006.00012; Hollywood Pops Orchestra (Box 6)
    Hairston featured as artist./ This date is approximate./ Hollywood, CA./ Capitol./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Hail, America!, 1962; MS040.001.007.00001; Dragon, Carmen (Box 7)
    Inscribed to Margaret (possibly Marge Hairston) from Marjorie Cranford./ This date is approximate./ [United States]./ RCA./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and accompanying material included./
  - Hal Leonard presents Savor the flavors for choral ensemble, 1977-1978, MS040.001.007.00002; Lojeski, Ed (Box 7)
    Hairston featured as artist./ Winona, MN./ Hal Leonard Publishing./ 2 sound discs: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Hal Leonard presents Savor the flavors for choral ensemble, 1978-1979, MS040.001.007.00003; Kerr, Anita (Box 7)
    Hairston featured as artist./ This date is approximate./ Milwaukee, WI./ Hal Leonard Publishing./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and descriptive booklet included./
  - Hal Leonard's music for choral ensemble, 1979-1980, MS040.001.007.00004; Unknown (Box 7)
    Hairston featured as artist./ Milwaukee, WI./ Hal Leonard Publishing./ 2 sound discs: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch [and] 45 rpm, 7-inch./ Original record jacket and letter to Jester Hairston included./
  - Haystack '73 choir, 1973; MS040.001.007.00005; Haystack Choir (Box 7)
    Hairston featured as artist and director./ Portland, OR./ Century Records./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - The Henry Sibley high school choirs 1980 present An evening with Jester Hairston, 1979; MS040.001.007.00006; Henry Sibley High School Choirs (Box 7)
    Hairston featured as artist and director./ [United States]./ Melody Recording./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - The Henry Sibley high school choirs present An evening with Jester Hairston, 1977; MS040.001.007.00007; Henry Sibley High School Choirs (Box 7)
  - Hilltop junior high school band and orchestra and glee clubs, 1962; MS040.001.007.00008; Hilltop junior high school band, chorus, and glee clubs (Box 7)
    Inscribed to Hairston by the Hilltop Girls Glee Club./ Saugus, CA./ Century./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Il tramonto, 1978; MS040.001.007.00009; Ballinger, Cathryn (Box 7)
    Inscribed to Hairston from Cathryn Ballinger./ Malibu, CA./ Orion./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Jester Hairston choral festival, 1972; MS040.001.007.00010; McNary High School (Box 7)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ Salem, OR./ Century./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - The Jester Hairston collection, 1984; MS040.001.007.00011; Hairston, Jester (Box 7)
    Hairston featured as artist./ This date is approximate./ Waco, TX./ Light./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - The Jester Hairston collection, 1984; MS040.001.007.00012; Hairston, Jester (Box 7)
  - Jester Hairston concert with the Utah State University Chorale, 1970; MS040.001.008.00001; Utah State University Chorale (Box 8)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ New York./ Murbo./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Jester Hairston concert with the Utah State University Chorale, 1970; MS040.001.008.00002; Utah State University Chorale (Box 8)
  - Jester Hairston conducts a program of spirituals, 1979; MS040.001.008.00003; La Jolla Presbyterian Chancel Choir (Box 8)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ Oaks, CA./ Discs./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Jester Hairston conducts the Westminster high school choir, 1970; MS040.001.008.00004; Westminster High School Choir (Box 8)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ Huntington Station, NY./ Silver Crest Custom./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Jester Hairston Metropolitan Choir, 1950; MS040.001.008.00005 (Box 8)
    Hairston featured as artist./ This date is approximate./ [United States]./ Dick Spaulding Recording./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./
  - Jester Hairston Metropolitan Choir, 1950; MS040.001.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Jester Hairston Metropolitan Choir, 1950; MS040.001.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - Jester Hairston negro spiritual concert, 1962; MS040.001.008.00008; East San Diego Presbyterian Church (Box 8)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ Hollywood, CA./ Location Recording Service./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./
  - Jester Hairston negro spiritual concert, 1962; MS040.001.008.00009; East San Diego Presbyterian Church (Box 8)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ Hollywood, CA./ Location Recording Service./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Jester Hairston TV special with the Utah State University Chorale, 1970; MS040.001.008.00010; Utah State University Chorale (Box 8)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ New York./ Murbo Records./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Jester Hairston TV special with the Utah State University Chorale, 1970; MS040.001.008.00011; Utah State University Chorale (Box 8)
  - Jester Hairston TV special with the Utah State University Chorale, 1970; MS040.001.008.00012; Utah State University Chorale (Box 8)
  - Jester Hairston TV special with the Utah State University Chorale, 1970; MS040.001.008.00013; Utah State University Chorale (Box 8)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ New York./ Murbo Records./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./
  - Joyously we sing, 1979; MS040.001.008.00014; Shambrey Chorale (Box 8)
    Hairston featured as artist./ Los Angles, CA./ [S.I.]./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Jus' keep on singin', 1965; MS040.001.008.00015; Anderson, Marian (Box 8)
    Notation by Jester Hairston, possibly related via Hall Johnson./ [New York]./ RCA Victor./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and operating guide included./
  - Kansas State University All-state music clinic, 1969; MS040.001.009.00001; Kansas State University (Box 9)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ Lawrence, KA./ Audio House./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./
  - Litchfield High School highlights of 1971, MS040.001.009.00002; Litchfield High School Choir, Wind Ensemble, and Band (Box 9)
    Signed by Nancy Christianson./ Minneapolis, MN./ Sound 80, Inc../ 2 sound discs: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Madjazz, 1984; MS040.001.009.00003 (Box 9)
    Hairston featured as artist. Inscribed to Hairston from Bill White./ Minneapolis, MN./ Custom Recording./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Merry Christmas, 1965; MS040.001.009.00004; Williams, Andy (Box 9)
    Hairston featured as artist. This date is approximate./ [New York]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - The Milikin Choir, 1972; MS040.001.009.00005 (Box 9)
    Inscribed to Hairston by Richard Hoffland./ [United States]./ Delta Records./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - The Ministry of Music, South Main Baptist Church presents Christmas with Jester, 1982; MS040.001.009.00006; South Main Baptist Church (Box 9)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ This date is approximate./ Houston, TX./ South Main Baptist Church./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./ Of the five sealed and four unsealed copies of this record, two of each type should be retained permanently. The other five copies may be considered for donation.
  - The Ministry of Music, South Main Baptist Church presents Christmas with Jester, 1982; MS040.001.009.00007; South Main Baptist Church (Box 9)
  - The Ministry of Music, South Main Baptist Church presents Christmas with Jester, 1982; MS040.001.009.00008; South Main Baptist Church (Box 9)
  - The Ministry of Music, South Main Baptist Church presents Christmas with Jester, 1982; MS040.001.009.00009; South Main Baptist Church (Box 9)
  - The Ministry of Music, South Main Baptist Church presents Christmas with Jester, 1982; MS040.001.009.00010; South Main Baptist Church (Box 9)
  - The Ministry of Music, South Main Baptist Church presents Christmas with Jester, 1982; MS040.001.009.00011; South Main Baptist Church (Box 9)
  - The Ministry of Music, South Main Baptist Church presents Christmas with Jester, 1982; MS040.001.009.00012; South Main Baptist Church (Box 9)
  - The Ministry of Music, South Main Baptist Church presents Christmas with Jester, 1982; MS040.001.009.00013; South Main Baptist Church (Box 9)
  - The Ministry of Music, South Main Baptist Church presents Christmas with Jester, 1982; MS040.001.009.00014; South Main Baptist Church (Box 9)
  - O for a thousand tongues, 1970; MS040.001.010.00001; South Main Baptist Church (Box 10)
    Inscribed to Hairston from Vida Havard [?]./ This date is approximate./ Waco, TX./ World Records, Inc./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Out of the mouth of babes comes perfect praise, 1970; MS040.001.010.00002; Figueroa Little Angel Chorus (Box 10)
    Hairston featured as artist./ This date is approximate./ [United States]./ [S.I.]./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - The Pacific Music Camp presents the Pacific Choral Clinic, 1951; MS040.001.010.00003; Pacific Music Camp (Box 10)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ [United States]./ [S.I.]./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - The Pacific Music Camp presents the Pacific Choral Clinic, 1951; MS040.001.010.00004; Pacific Music Camp (Box 10)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ [United States]./ [S.I.]./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./
  - [The Pacific Music Camp] Jester Hairston rehearses Pacific Music Clinic, Stockton, 1957-02-09; MS040.001.010.00005; Pacific Music Camp (Box 10)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ Stockton, CA./ Quality Recording Service./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./
  - The Pacific Music Camp, 1960; MS040.001.010.00006; Pacific Music Camp (Box 10)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ This date is approximate./ Stockton, CA./ Quality Recording Service./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./
  - The Pacific Music Camp all camp chorale, 1958; MS040.001.010.00007; Pacific Music Camp (Box 10)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ Stockton, CA./ Quality Recording Service./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - The Pacific Music Camp all camp chorale, 1958; MS040.001.010.00008; Pacific Music Camp (Box 10)
  - The Pacific Music Camp Pacific Music Clinic Band [and orchestra and chorus], 1958; MS040.001.010.00009; Pacific Music Camp (Box 10)
  - The Pacific Music Clinic, 1959; MS040.001.010.00010; Pacific Music Camp (Box 10)
  - The Pacific Music Clinic, 1959; MS040.001.010.00011; Pacific Music Camp (Box 10)
  - Paidite Z Menaj [Go my way], 1973; MS040.001.010.00012; The Ballard Chorale (Box 10)
    Hairston featured as conductor and artist./ Record jacket and sleeve are inscibed to Jester Hairston./ [United States]./ Century Records./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and sleeve included./
  - Placentia United School District in concert with Jester, 1970; MS040.001.010.00013; Placentia United School District (Box 10)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ This date is approximate./ [United States]./ [S.I/]./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Prairie View A & M University Chorale, 1969; MS040.001.010.00014 (Box 10)
    Signed by Robert A. Henry./ Austin, TX./ A.C.R. Kno Bel./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - A profile of Negro life in song, 1965; MS040.001.011.00001; Hairston, Jester (Box 11)
    Hairston featured as artist./ New York./ Murbo Records./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./ Records 00001-00006 in this box have identical titles, songs lists, and publishing information. However, record 00001 has a different cover than records 00002-00006./
  - A profile of Negro life in song, 1965; MS040.001.011.00002; Hairston, Jester (Box 11)
  - A profile of Negro life in song, 1965; MS040.001.011.00003; Hairston, Jester (Box 11)
  - A profile of Negro life in song, 1965; MS040.001.011.00004; Hairston, Jester (Box 11)
  - A profile of Negro life in song, 1965; MS040.001.011.00005; Hairston, Jester (Box 11)
  - A profile of Negro life in song, 1965; MS040.001.011.00006; Hairston, Jester (Box 11)
  - A profile of the Negro spiritual, 1973; MS040.001.011.00007; Hairston, Jester (Box 11)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ [California]./ [S.I.]./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - A profile of the Negro spiritual, 1973; MS040.001.011.00008; Hairston, Jester (Box 11)
  - Sacred music at Texas Luthern College, 1951; MS040.001.011.00009; Texas Lutheran College Choir (Box 11)
    Notations on back of record jacket./ This date is approximate./ Camden, NJ./ RCA Victor./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - The Sanctuary Choir of the North Long Beach Methodist Church, 1955; MS040.001.011.00010 (Box 11)
    Inscribed to Hairston by members of the choir./ This date is approximate./ [United States]./ [S.I.]./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Stairway of the stars, 1974; MS040.001.011.00011; Santa Monica Unified School District (Box 11)
    Hairston featured as artist and guest conductor./ Burbank, CA./ Location Recording Service./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - A session of Afro-American folk songs, 1983; MS040.001.011.00012; University of Mississippi Concert Singers (Box 11)
    Hairston featured as artist and clinician./ Burbank, CA./ Location Recording Service./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./
  - Sibley High School Choir, 1971; MS040.001.011.00013; Henry Sibley High School Choirs (Box 11)
    Photograph of Hairston on back cover, relationship not indicated./ [United States]./ [S.I.]./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and accompanying material included./
  - Singing Sergeants choral masterworks, 1986; MS040.001.011.00014; Singing Sergeants (Box 11)
    Notation on original record sleeve./ [United States]./ [United States Air Force]./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and sleeve included./
  - Song and dance man, 1981; MS040.001.012.00001; California Fever (Box MS040 Shared 1)
    Signed by Tim McDonald./ This date is approximate./ [United States]./ [S.I.]./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - A song for Christmas, 1963; MS040.001.012.00002; Mantovani and his Orchestra (Box MS040 Shared 1)
    Hairston featured as artist./ This date is approximate./ London./ Full Frequency Range Recording./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Songs of enchantment, 1963; MS040.001.012.00003; Terri, Salli (Box MS040 Shared 1)
    Inscribed to Hairston from Salli Terri./ This date is approximate./ [Hollywood, CA]./ Capital Records./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and sleeve included./
  - Soundstation '77, 1977; MS040.001.012.00004; Edmonds Community College (Box MS040 Shared 1)
    Inscribed to Hairston from Frank DeMiero./ [Dallas, TX]./ [A & R Record Manufacturing Corporation]./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and sleeve included./
  - The Student prince, 1980; MS040.001.012.00005; Chores und Orchesters der Hamburgischen Staatsoper (Box MS040 Shared 1)
    Incribed to Hairston from 'Gertrud, Werner and Andreas'./ Germany./ Kanon./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and accompanying material included./
  - Symphonic spirituals, 1979; MS040.001.012.00006; The Royal Philharmonic Orchestra of London (Box MS040 Shared 1)
    Includes three sheets of music inside the record jacket entitled "Musical Introduction of Jester Hairston" by [Cousin] Jackie Hairston./ [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket, sleeve, and accompanying material included./
  - Tenderly, 1950; MS040.001.012.00007; Peterson, Oscar (Box MS040 Shared 1)
    Signed by Marge Hairston./ United States./ Clef Records./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Then sings my soul, 1974; MS040.001.012.00008; Frank, Fred (Box MS040 Shared 1)
    Inscribed to Marge and Jester Hairston from Fred Frank./ Waco, TX./ World Records./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Twelve songs of Christmas, 1963; MS040.001.012.00009; Reeves, Jim (Box MS040 Shared 1)
    Hairston featured as artist./ [New York]./ RCA./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Viking Songfest, 1955; MS040.001.012.00010; North Salem High School (Box MS040 Shared 1)
    Hairston featured as artist./ Salem, OR./ Wayne Meusey./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Lullaby/I wonder as I wander, 1960; MS040.001.012.00011; The Walter Schumann Singers (Box MS040 Shared 1)
    Hairston featured as artist on second disc [MS040.001.012.00011]./ This date is approximate./ Salem, OR./ Wayne Meusey./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./
  - Rocka my soul/ Oh holy land, 1960; MS040.001.012.00012; The Walter Schumann Singers (Box MS040 Shared 1)
    Hairston featured as artist, notations on original record sleeve./ This date is approximate./ Salem, OR./ Wayne Meusey./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record sleeve included./
  - Wartburg Choir, 1971; MS040.001.012.00013 (Box MS040 Shared 1)
    Hairston featured as artist./ [United States]./ Mark Custom Recording./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Weber State College choral music festival with Dr. Jester Hairston, 1970; MS040.001.013.00001; Weber State College (Box 13)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ This date is approximate./ Camden, NJ./ Recorded Publications Company./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./
  - We know we shall live, 1981; MS040.001.013.00002; Johnson, Nana Simi (Box 13)
    Inscribed to Marge and Jester Hairston from Nana Simi Johnson./ Nashville, TN./ Great Circle Records./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - The Winston-Salem State University Choir sings "Ev'ry time I feel the Spririt" and other selections, 1970; MS040.001.013.00003; The Winston-Salem State University Choir (Box 13)
    Signed by James Dillard./ This date is approximate./ Winston-Salem, NC./ Triad Records./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - A world of Christmas music, 1972; MS040.001.013.00004; The Sanctuary Choirs (Box 13)
    Hairston featured as artist and conductor./ Waco, TX./ World Records./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./